* 

* USD
    
    CAD
    
    EUR

 USD

 CAD

 EUR

 USD

 CAD

 EUR

Find a location

**C**

* ### By Region
    
* ### By Options
    
* ### Popular Locations

Dedicated servers in 146 locations worldwide
============================================

©

### 

Legal

Effective date: 2024-05-31

Updated on: 2024-05-21

This Privacy Policy explains the policies of OneProvider on the collection and use of the information we collect when you access [https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/) (the “Service”). This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights and how you are protected under privacy laws.

By using our Service, you are consenting to the collection and use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please do not access or use our Service if you do not consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy has been created with the help of [CookieScript Privacy Policy Generator](https://cookie-script.com/privacy-policy-generator).

OneProvider is authorized to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. This may occur without prior notice.

OneProvider will post the revised Privacy Policy on the [https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/) website

### Collection and Use of Your Personal Information

Information We Collect
----------------------

When using our Service, you will be prompted to provide us with personal information used to contact or identify you. [https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/) collects the following information:

* Usage Data
    
* Name
    
* Email
    
* Mobile Number
    
* Work Address
    
* Payment Information
    
* Home Address
    
* Company Name

Usage Data includes the following:

* Internet Protocol (IP) address of computers accessing the site
    
* Web page requests
    
* Referring web pages
    
* Browser used to access site
    
* Time and date of access

How We Collect Information
--------------------------

[https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/) collects and receives information from you in the following manner:

* When you fill a registration form or otherwise submit your personal information.

Your information will be stored for up to 1095 days after it is no longer required to provide you the services. Your information may be retained for longer periods for reporting or record- keeping in accordance with applicable laws. Information which does not identify you personally may be stored indefinitely.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

[https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/) may use your information for the following purposes:

* **Providing and maintaining our Service,** as well as monitoring the usage of our Service.
    
* **Managing your account.** Your Personal Data can enable access to multiple functions of our Service that are available to registered users.
    
* **To contact you.** OneProvider will contact you by email, phone, SMS, or another form of electronic communication related to the functions, products, services, or security updates when necessary or reasonable.
    
* **To update you** with news, general information, special offers, new services, and events.
    
* **Marketing and promotional initiatives.** OneProvider will use non-specific information gathered from you in order to improve our marketing efforts.
    
* **Testimonials and customer feedback collection.** If you share a testimonial or review about your experience using our Service, it will be shared or otherwise used on the website.
    
* **Managing customer orders.** Your email address, phone number, social media profiles, and other user account information will be used in order to manage orders placed through our Service.
    
* **Dispute resolution and site protection.** Your information will be used in the instance of a legal dispute to resolve issues related to our Service.
    
* **For the performance of a contract.** Your Personal Data will assist with the development, undertaking, and compliance of a purchase contract for products or services you have purchased through our Service.
    
* **Targeted advertising.** Your Personal Data will be used to improve advertising efforts that are relevant to your specific interests.

How We Share Your Information
-----------------------------

OneProvider will share your information, when applicable, in the following situations:

* **With your consent.** OneProvider will share your information for any purpose with your explicit consent.

Third-party Sharing
-------------------

Any third party we share your information with must disclose the purpose for which they intend to use your information. They must retain your information only for the duration disclosed when requesting or receiving said information. The third-party service provider must not further collect, sell, or use your personal information except as necessary to perform the specified purpose.

Your information may be shared to a third-party for reasons including:

* **Analytics information.** Your information might be shared with online analytics tools in order to track and analyse website traffic.
    
* **Payment processing and recovery services.** Your information will be used in order to process payments in the event of a purchase, refund, or other similar request.
    
* **Improving targeted advertising campaigns.** OneProvider partners with third party service providers to improve targeted advertising campaigns.

If you choose to provide such information during registration or otherwise, you are giving OneProvider permission to use, share, and store that information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Your information may be disclosed for additional reasons, including:

* Complying with applicable laws, regulations, or court orders.
    
* Responding to claims that your use of our Service violates third-party rights.
    
* Enforcing agreements you make with us, including this Privacy Policy.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. Websites use cookies to help users navigate efficiently and perform certain functions. Cookies that are required for the website to operate properly are allowed to be set without your permission. All other cookies need to be approved before they can be set in the browser.

* **Strictly necessary cookies.** Strictly necessary cookies allow core website functionality such as user login and account management. The website cannot be used properly without strictly necessary cookies.
    
* **Targeting cookies.** Targeting cookies are used to identify visitors between different websites, eg. content partners, banner networks. Those cookies may be used by companies to build a profile of visitor interests or show relevant ads on other websites.
    
* **Performance cookies.** Performance cookies are used to see how visitors use the website, eg. analytics cookies. Those cookies cannot be used to directly identify a certain visitor.
    
* **Functionality cookies.** Functionality cookies are used to remember visitor information on the website, eg. language, timezone, enhanced content.

You can change your consent to cookie usage below.

Security
--------

Your information’s security is important to us. [https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/) utilizes a range of security measures to prevent the misuse, loss, or alteration of the information you have given us. However, because we cannot guarantee the security of the information you provide us, you must access our service at your own risk.

OneProvider is not responsible for the performance of websites operated by third parties or your interactions with them. When you leave this website, we recommend you review the privacy practices of other websites you interact with and determine the adequacy of those practices.

Contact Us
----------

For any questions, please contact us through the following methods:

Name: OneProvider

Address: 3275 Av Francis-Hughes, Laval, QC H7L 5A5 Canada

Email: [info@oneprovider.com](mailto:info@oneprovider.com)

Website: [https://oneprovider.com](https://oneprovider.com/)

Phone: + 1 (800) 380-5112

* Dedicated Servers
* ONECLOUD
* Features
* About

#### Products

#### Client

#### About

#### Legal

© OneProvider.com 2016. All rights reserved. A BrainStorm Network Inc. company

OneProvider uses cookies for functional and analytics purposes. [Learn more](https://oneprovider.com/about-us/privacy-policy)  
  
Got it!
